export const spanishDeck = [
    {
        "Question": "¡Hola!",
        "Answer": "Hello!"
    },
    {
        "Question": "¿Cómo estás?",
        "Answer": "How are you?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Gracias.",
        "Answer": "Thank you."
    },
    {
        "Question": "De nada.",
        "Answer": "You're welcome."
    },
    {
        "Question": "Perdón.",
        "Answer": "Excuse me."
    },
    {
        "Question": "¡Adiós!",
        "Answer": "Goodbye!"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Hasta luego.",
        "Answer": "See you later."
    },
    {
        "Question": "¿Cómo te llamas?",
        "Answer": "What is your name?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Me llamo...",
        "Answer": "My name is..."
    },
    {
        "Question": "¿Dónde está el baño?",
        "Answer": "Where is the bathroom?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "No entiendo.",
        "Answer": "I don't understand."
    },
    {
        "Question": "¿Cuánto cuesta?",
        "Answer": "How much does it cost?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "¿Habla inglés?",
        "Answer": "Do you speak English?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "¿Qué significa?",
        "Answer": "What does it mean?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Tengo hambre.",
        "Answer": "I'm hungry."
    },
    {
        "Question": "Tengo sed.",
        "Answer": "I'm thirsty."
    },
    {
        "Question": "¿Dónde puedo encontrar un restaurante?",
        "Answer": "Where can I find a restaurant?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Estoy perdido.",
        "Answer": "I'm lost."
    },
    {
        "Question": "Ayúdame, por favor.",
        "Answer": "Please help me."
    },
    {
        "Question": "¿Cómo llego a...?",
        "Answer": "How do I get to...?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "¿Dónde está el banco?",
        "Answer": "Where is the bank?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "¿Hay restaurantes cerca?",
        "Answer": "Are there any restaurants nearby?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "¿Cómo llego al museo?",
        "Answer": "How do I get to the museum?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Estoy perdido. ¿Puedes ayudarme a encontrar el hotel?",
        "Answer": "I'm lost. Can you help me find the hotel?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "¿Qué recomiendas visitar en esta ciudad?",
        "Answer": "What do you recommend visiting in this city?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "¿Cómo reservo una mesa en un restaurante?",
        "Answer": "How do I book a table at a restaurant?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "¿Dónde puedo encontrar una farmacia?",
        "Answer": "Where can I find a pharmacy?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "¿Cuál es el horario de la tienda?",
        "Answer": "What are the store's working hours?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Quiero comprar un recuerdo.",
        "Answer": "I would like to buy a souvenir."
    },
    {
        "Question": "¿Cuál es tu restaurante favorito en esta ciudad?",
        "Answer": "What's your favorite restaurant in this city?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "¿Puedes tomarme una foto, por favor?",
        "Answer": "Can you take a photo of me, please?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "¿Dónde puedo ir a un concierto?",
        "Answer": "Where can I go for a concert?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "¿Qué tan lejos está el parque más cercano?",
        "Answer": "How far is the nearest park?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "¿Dónde puedo encontrar información sobre atracciones turísticas?",
        "Answer": "Where can I find information about tourist attractions?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "¿Puedo pedir un taxi?",
        "Answer": "Can I order a taxi?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "¿Cuál es el museo más famoso de esta ciudad?",
        "Answer": "What is the most famous museum in this city?"
    },
    {
        "Question": "¿Tienes recomendaciones para cafeterías locales?",
        "Answer": "Do you have any recommendations for local cafes?"
    }
];
